so she tells us you can go in you can go
in you can't go in now I'm think she
talking to my friend because my friend
is a realtor right um and she says no
you can't go in and I said why can't I
go in she says you're just on the list
to not be able to go in now I had also
been invited to this party directly by
Jesse Williams right so then Elijah is
like well I'm one of the planners of the
party so they can't stop you from they
can't got me from bringing you in so he
starts to bring me in and home girl
grabs my arm but I remember when I told
you I've been in New Yorker since I was
12 shake that off yeah lose me yeah
crazy so we go in the party and I go and
sit down no sorry I go in the party I go
by the bar my home girl goes to the
bathroom I'm standing by the bar and a
security guard approaches me uh oh a
security guard your size approaches me
and says hey um I'm going to have to ask
you to leave